A Guide to the Luther Porter Jackson Papers, 1772-1960
Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
- SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE
  - B. Office Correspondence
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Dec 1941 (Box-folder 6:142)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Jan 1942 (Box-folder 6:143)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Feb 1942 (Box-folder 6:144)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Mar 1942 (Box-folder 6:145)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Apr-May 1942 (Box-folder 6:146)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. June-July 1942 (Box-folder 6:147)
    - Office Correspondence- Jackson Luther P. Aug 1942 (Box-folder 6:148)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Sept 1942 (Box-folder 6:149)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Oct 1942 (Box-folder 6:150)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Nov 1942 (Box-folder 6:151)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Dec 1942 (Box-folder 6:152)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Jan 1943 (Box-folder 6:153)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Feb 1943 (Box-folder 6:154)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Feb 16-28, 1943 (Box-folder 6:155)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Mar 1-15, 1943 (Box-folder 7:156)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Mar 16-31, 1943 (Box-folder 7:157)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. April 1-15, 1943 (Box-folder 7:158)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. April 16-31, 1943 (Box-folder 7:159)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. May 1943 (Box-folder 7:160)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. May 16-31 1943 (Box-folder 7:161)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. June 1943 (Box-folder 7:162)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. July 1943 (Box-folder 7:163)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Sept-Oct 1943 (Box-folder 7:164)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Nov 1-18, 1943 (Box-folder 7:165)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. (Box-folder 7:)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Nov 19-29, 1943 (Box-folder 7:166)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Dec 1-15, 1943 (Box-folder 7:167)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Dec 16-31 1943 (Box-folder 7:168)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Jan 1-20, 1944 (Box-folder 7:169)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Jan 21-31, 1944 (Box-folder 7: 170)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Feb 1-15, 1944 (Box-folder 7:171)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Feb 16-29, 1944 (Box-folder 7:172)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Mar. 1-15, 1944 (Box-folder 8:173)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Mar 16-31, 1944 (Box-folder 8:174)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Apr 1-14, 1944 (Box-folder 8:175)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. April 16-31, 1944 (Box-folder 8:176)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. May 1944 (Box-folder 8:177)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. June 1944 (Box-folder 8:178)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. July 1944 (Box-folder 8:179)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Aug 1944 (Box-folder 8:180)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Sept 1-14, 1944 (Box-folder 8:181)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Sept 16-31, 1944 (Box-folder 8:182)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Oct 1944 (Box-folder 8:183)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Nov 1944 (Box-folder 8:184)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Dec 1944 (Box-folder 8:185)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Jan 1945 (Box-folder 8:186)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Feb 1945 (Box-folder 8:187)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Feb 15-29, 1945 (Box-folder 8:188)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Mar 1945 (Box-folder 9:189)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. April 1945 (Box-folder 9:190)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. May 1945 (Box-folder 9:191)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. May 16-31, 1941 (Box-folder 9:192)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. June 1945 (Box-folder 9:193)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. (Box-folder 9:)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. July 1941 (Box-folder 9:194)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Aug 1945 (Box-folder 9:195)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Sept 1945 (Box-folder 9:196)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Oct 1945 (Box-folder 9:197)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Nov 1945 (Box-folder 9:198)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Dec 1945 (Box-folder 9:199)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Jan 1-16, 1946 (Box-folder 9:200)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Jan 17-31, 1946 (Box-folder 9:201)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Feb 1-15, 1946 (Box-folder 9:202)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Feb 16-28, 1946 (Box-folder 9:203)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Mar 1-8, 1946 (Box-folder 9:204)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Mar 9-13, 1946 (Box-folder 9:205)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Mar 14-19, 1946 (Box-folder 10:206)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Mar 20-31, 1946 (Box-folder 10:207)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. April 1-15, 1946 (Box-folder 10:208)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. April 16-31, 1946 (Box-folder 10:209)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. May 1946 (Box-folder 10:210)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. June 1-20, 1946 (Box-folder 10:211)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. June 21- 31, 1946 (Box-folder 10:212)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. July 1-15, 1946 (Box-folder 10:213)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. July 19-31, 1946 (Box-folder 10:214)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Aug 1946 (Box-folder 10:215)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Sept 1946 (Box-folder 10:216)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Oct 1946 (Box-folder 10:217)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Nov 1946 (Box-folder 10:218)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Dec 1946 (Box-folder 10:219)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Jan 1947 (Box-folder 11:220)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Feb 1947 (Box-folder 11:221)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Mar 1947 (Box-folder 11:222)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. April 1947 (Box-folder 11:223)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. May 1947 (Box-folder 11:224)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. June 1947 (Box-folder 11:225)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. July 1947 (Box-folder 11:226)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Aug 1947 (Box-folder 11:227)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Sept 1947 (Box-folder 11:228)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Oct 1947 (Box-folder 11:229)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Nov 1947 (Box-folder 11:230)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Dec 1947 (Box-folder 11:231)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Jan 1948 (Box-folder 11:232)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Feb 1948 (Box-folder 11:233)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. March-April 1948 (Box-folder 11:234)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. May 1948 (Box-folder 12:235)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. June 1948 (Box-folder 12:236)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. July 1948 (Box-folder 12:237)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Aug 1948 (Box-folder 12:238)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Sept 1948 (Box-folder 12:239)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Oct 1948 (Box-folder 12:240)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Nov 1948 (Box-folder 12:241)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Dec 1948 (Box-folder 12:242)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Jan 1949 (Box-folder 12:243)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Feb 1949 (Box-folder 12:244)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Mar-Apr 1949 (Box-folder 12:245)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. May 1949 (Box-folder 12:246)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Jun 1949 (Box-folder 12:247)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Jul-Aug 1949 (Box-folder 12:248)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Sept 1949 (Box-folder 12:249)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Oct-Dec 1949 (Box-folder 12:250)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Jan 1950 (Box-folder 12:251)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Feb-Mar 1950 (Box-folder 12:252)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. Apr 1950 (Box-folder 12:253)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. n.d. (Box-folder 12:254)
    - Office Correspondence-Jackson, Luther P. n.d. (Box-folder 12:255)
  - C. Personal 1918- 1960
    - Correspondence-Adelaide 1947 (Box-folder 13:256)
    - Correspondence--Alice and James 1946 (Box-folder 13:257)
    - Correspondence--Allen, M. C. 1957 (Box-folder 13:258)
    - Correspondence--Allen, Russell A. (Mrs.) 1950 (Box-folder 13:259)
    - Correspondence--Alice 1945 (Box-folder 13:260)
    - Correspondence--Allison, Andrew J. 1935 (Box-folder 13:261)
    - Correspondence--Anderson, Felicia 1925-1945 (Box-folder 13:262)
    - Correspondence--Anderson, Julia M. 1943-1948 (Box-folder 13:263)
    - Correspondence--Artiatura 1948, n.d. (Box-folder 13:264)
    - Correspondence--Artis Vernon 1949 (Box-folder 13:265)
    - Correspondence--Ardrades 1946 (Box-folder 13:266)
    - Correspondence--Baker, Helen 1942-1949 (Box-folder 13:267)
    - Correspondence--B. G., Esdilia 1937 (Box-folder 13:268)
    - Correspondence--B., Jimmie 1949 (Box-folder 13:269)
    - Correspondence--Baker, Jim 1946 (Box-folder 13:270)
    - Correspondence--Baker, Jr. Percy 1945 (Box-folder 13:271)
    - Correspondence--Baker, Ruth n.d. (Box-folder 13:272)
    - Correspondence--Ball, Sadie E. 1941 (Box-folder 13:273)
    - Correspondence--Banks, W. Lester 1950-1957 (Box-folder 13:274)
    - Correspondence--Bates, Phillip H. 1947 (Box-folder 13:275)
    - Correspondence--Bea, A. C. n.d. (Box-folder 13:276)
    - Correspondence--Bea 1950 (Box-folder 13:277)
    - Correspondence--Becky 1944-1946 (Box-folder 13:278)
    - Correspondence--Belinda 1938-1940 (Box-folder 13:279)
    - Correspondence--Berrei, Mildred 1943 (Box-folder 13:280)
    - Correspondence--Bess 1938 (Box-folder 13:281)
    - Correspondence--Bibbins, Rose 1934 (Box-folder 13:282)
    - Correspondence--Blambie 1942 (Box-folder 13:283)
    - Correspondence--Bowen, I.T. 1954 (Box-folder 13:284)
    - Correspondence--Bowling, Richard H. 1954 (Box-folder 13:285)
    - Correspondence--Boyle, Patty 1946 (Box-folder 13:286)
    - Correspondence--Brakenborough, B.F. 1946 (Box-folder 13:287)
    - Correspondence--Broadeax, Dorothy Mae 1941-1942 (Box-folder 13:288)
    - Correspondence--Brooks Albert M.D. 1957 (Box-folder 13:289)
    - Correspondence--Brown, Lucy Ella (Miss) 1944 (Box-folder 13:290)
    - Correspondence--Brace, Irmalou 1948 (Box-folder 13:291)
    - Correspondence--Brucker, Howard 1957 (Box-folder 13:292)
    - Correspondence--Burke, C.P. 1943 (Box-folder 13:293)
    - Correspondence--Burke, Jessie L. 1944 (Box-folder 13:294)
    - Correspondence--Burke, Maude L. 1944 (Box-folder 13:295)
    - Correspondence-- (Box-folder 13:)
    - Correspondence--Buster, Katie Patterson 1947 (Box-folder 13:296)
    - Correspondence--Caldwell, Etta Jane 1948 (Box-folder 13:297)
    - Correspondence--Calvin 1948 (Box-folder 13:298)
    - Correspondence--Capp, Hallie T. 1950 (Box-folder 13:299)
    - Correspondence--Chamberlain, Mary E. 1943 (Box-folder 13:300)
    - Correspondence--Charles 1944 (Box-folder 13:301)
    - Correspondence--Chavis 1949 (Box-folder 13:302)
    - Correspondence--Chew, Anna L. 1942 (Box-folder 13:303)
    - Correspondence--Chummie 1935-1949 (Box-folder 13:304)
    - Correspondence--Church of Christ n.d. (Box-folder 13:305)
    - Correspondence--Churchill 1945-1946 (Box-folder 13:306)
    - Correspondence--Clark, B.M. 1942-1949 (Box-folder 13:307)
    - Correspondence--Clark, B.N. Taylor 1946 (Box-folder 13:308)
    - Correspondence--Collins, Cleota 1943 (Box-folder 13:309)
    - Correspondence--Cook, Ella F. 1921-1937 (Box-folder 13:310)
    - Correspondence--Cook, Mary Wood 1946 (Box-folder 13:311)
    - Correspondence--Cooley, Dennis R. 1944 (Box-folder 13:312)
    - Correspondence--Cooper n.d. (Box-folder 13:313)
    - Correspondence--Cox, Reacie M. 1945-1948 (Box-folder 13:314)
    - Correspondence--D'Albert, Marc 1942 (Box-folder 14:315)
    - Correspondence--Dabney, Thomas L. 1963 (Box-folder 14:316)
    - Correspondence--Daily Word n.d. (Box-folder 14:317)
    - Correspondence--Daniel, Robert P. 1953 (Box-folder 14:318)
    - Correspondence--Davis, Aldena W. (Mrs.) 1948 (Box-folder 14:319)
    - Correspondence--Davis, Fay 1946 (Box-folder 14:320)
    - Correspondence--Davis, Willie C. 1960 (Box-folder 14:321)
    - Correspondence--Dawson, Elizabeth (Mrs.) 1955 (Box-folder 14:322)
    - Correspondence--Day, Marie Culture 1949 (Box-folder 14:323)
    - Correspondence--Demby, M.H. 1926 (Box-folder 14:324)
    - Correspondence--Dennison, W.W. II n.d. (Box-folder 14:325)
    - Correspondence--Divalidly 1941 (Box-folder 14:326)
    - Correspondence--Dix, Juanita Bowen 1947 (Box-folder 14:327)
    - Correspondence--Dorsey, Warren 1946 (Box-folder 14:328)
    - Correspondence--Dorsey, William R. 1944 (Box-folder 14:329)
    - Correspondence--Doy, Luicille 1945 (Box-folder 14:330)
    - Correspondence--Dungee, John 1948 (Box-folder 14:331)
    - Correspondence--Dunlap, Norm 1948 (Box-folder 14:332)
    - Correspondence--Ernestine 1942 (Box-folder 14:333)
    - Correspondence--Evans, Mary G. 1918 (Box-folder 14:334)
    - Correspondence--Evans, Sandra E. 1947 (Box-folder 14:335)
    - Correspondence-- (Box-folder 14:)
    - Correspondence--Fannie 1948 (Box-folder 14:336)
    - Correspondence--Fay n.d. (Box-folder 14:337)
    - Correspondence--Fearonce, William H. 1964 (Box-folder 14:338)
    - Correspondence--Fleming, Maude 1941 (Box-folder 14:339)
    - Correspondence--Fortune, Annie Moore 1955 (Box-folder 14:340)
    - Correspondence--Foster, Mayme U. 1941-1942 (Box-folder 14:341)
    - Correspondence--Foster, Pocahontas 1925 (Box-folder 14:342)
    - Correspondence--Frances 1940-1944 (Box-folder 14:343)
    - Correspondence--Frazer, Lucille L. (Mrs.) 1950 (Box-folder 14:344)
    - Correspondence--Gandy, Barbara 1949 (Box-folder 14:345)
    - Correspondence--Gandy, Carrie B. n.d. (Box-folder 14:346)
    - Correspondence--Gandy, John M. 1923-1942 (Box-folder 14:347)
    - Correspondence--Gandy, Samuel L. 1953 (Box-folder 14:348)
    - Correspondence--Gaskin, V.B. 1945-1952 (Box-folder 14:349)
    - Correspondence--Giles, Vara T. n.d. (Box-folder 14:350)
    - Correspondence--Godfey, Beatrice 1947 (Box-folder 14:351)
    - Correspondence--Green, George n.d. (Box-folder 14:352)
    - Correspondence--Greenwood, Sadie Emaree 1944 (Box-folder 14:353)
    - Correspondence--Guard, Sara E. 1949 (Box-folder 14:354)
    - Correspondence--Hamlah, Beverly L. 1949 (Box-folder 14:355)
    - Correspondence--Harris, Emmie Alexander 1942 (Box-folder 14:356)
    - Correspondence--Harris, Ethel 1948 (Box-folder 14:357)
    - Correspondence--Harris, J. Everett 1918 (Box-folder 14:358)
    - Correspondence--Harrison, Madeline G. 1948 (Box-folder 14:359)
    - Correspondence--Hawkins, Bessie Branch 1946 (Box-folder 14:360)
    - Correspondence--Hazel 1939 (Box-folder 14:361)
    - Correspondence--Heard, Alexander 1951 (Box-folder 14:362)
    - Correspondence--Henrietta 1947 (Box-folder 14:363)
    - Correspondence--Hill, Bernice O. n.d. (Box-folder 14:364)
    - Correspondence--Hodge, Justine n.d. (Box-folder 14:365)
    - Correspondence--Holley, Mamie n.d. (Box-folder 14:366)
    - Correspondence--Howard, Helen Y. 1950 (Box-folder 14:367)
    - Correspondence--Howe, Rose C. 1944 (Box-folder 14:368)
    - Correspondence--Hunter, Louise Stores (Mrs.) 1945 (Box-folder 14:369)
    - Correspondence--Hurny 1937 (Box-folder 14:370)
    - Correspondence--Imogene 1947 (Box-folder 14:371)
    - Correspondence--India 1945 (Box-folder 14:372)
    - Correspondence--Inez 1948 (Box-folder 14:373)
    - Correspondence--Jackson, Eunice E. 1943 (Box-folder 15:374)
    - Correspondence--Jackson, (Frazer) Johnella 1927-1964 (Box-folder 15:375)
    - Correspondence--Jackson, Georgie 1946 (Box-folder 15:376)
    - Correspondence--Jackson, Laura F. 1931 (Box-folder 15:377)
    - Correspondence--Jackson, Jr. Luther Porter 1947 (Box-folder 15:378)
    - Correspondence--Jackson, Mae S. (Mrs.) 1955 (Box-folder 15:379)
    - Correspondence--Jackson, Thurston 1946 (Box-folder 15:380)
    - Correspondence--James (Rev. Mc.) n.d. (Box-folder 15:381)
    - Correspondence--Jean 1945 (Box-folder 15:382)
    - Correspondence--Jessie 1948 (Box-folder 15:383)
    - Correspondence--Jimmy 1945 (Box-folder 15:384)
    - Correspondence--Johns, Althea 1947, 1957 (Box-folder 15:385)
    - Correspondence--Johnson, Harry 1942-1943 (Box-folder 15:386)
    - Correspondence--Johnson, O.R. 1962 (Box-folder 15:387)
    - Correspondence--Jones, Janet Saunders 1950 (Box-folder 15:388)
    - Correspondence--Jones, Mattie A. 1949 (Box-folder 15:389)
    - Correspondence--Jones, Suejette 1941-1945 (Box-folder 15:390)
    - Correspondence--Kathleen n.d. (Box-folder 15:391)
    - Correspondence--King, John B. 1950 (Box-folder 15:392)
    - Correspondence--King, Wilson 1943-1947 (Box-folder 15:393)
    - Correspondence--Knight, Roy 1946-1947 (Box-folder 15:394)
    - Correspondence--Laforce, J.M. n.d. (Box-folder 15:395)
    - Correspondence--Lee, Everett 1946 (Box-folder 15:396)
    - Correspondence--Leftwich, Rosa Ross 1946 (Box-folder 15:397)
    - Correspondence--Leon 1946 (Box-folder 15:398)
    - Correspondence--Lewis, Leah V. 1946 (Box-folder 15:399)
    - Correspondence--Lewis, Mattie E. 1940 (Box-folder 15:400)
    - Correspondence--Lewis, R.H. 1943 (Box-folder 15:401)
    - Correspondence--Lindsay, Anna 1948-1949 (Box-folder 15:402)
    - Correspondence--Locklayer, Jr. John H. 1942, 1947 (Box-folder 15:403)
    - Correspondence--Logan, Spencer 1945-1946 (Box-folder 15:404)
    - Correspondence--Logan, Paul 1947 (Box-folder 15:405)
    - Correspondence--Lomax, Frances 1946 (Box-folder 15:406)
    - Correspondence--Lorraine 1944-1945 (Box-folder 15:407)
    - Correspondence--Louise 1944-1945 (Box-folder 15:408)
    - Correspondence--Louise, Mattie 1946 (Box-folder 15:409)
    - Correspondence--Lucille 1944-1955 (Box-folder 15:410)
    - Correspondence--Mackey, Carrie H. 1950 (Box-folder 15:411)
    - Correspondence--Maddy, Joseph E. 1949-1950 (Box-folder 15:412)
    - Correspondence--Marie 1949 (Box-folder 15:413)
    - Correspondence--McBrier, Vivian 1950 (Box-folder 15:414)
    - Correspondence--Murphy, Marion M. 1946 (Box-folder 15:415)
    - Correspondence--Nanette 1941 (Box-folder 15:416)
    - Correspondence--Nannie 1924 (Box-folder 15:417)
    - Correspondence--Nelson, James T. n.d. (Box-folder 15:418)
    - Correspondence--Olden, George 1942-1958 (Box-folder 15:419)
    - Correspondence--P., Juanita 1946 (Box-folder 15:420)
    - Correspondence--P. P. 1948 (Box-folder 15:421)
    - Correspondence--Page, M.R. (Mrs.) 1951 (Box-folder 15:422)
    - Correspondence--Payne, Helena M. 1961 (Box-folder 15:423)
    - Correspondence--Peoples, Emma Gillespie 1950 (Box-folder 15:424)
    - Correspondence--Perry, A. Geneva (Mrs.) 1948 (Box-folder 15:425)
    - Correspondence--Phillips, James T. 1947 (Box-folder 15:426)
    - Correspondence--Preston, Coralee E. 1942 (Box-folder 15:427)
    - Correspondence--Primas, R. 1955 (Box-folder 15:428)
    - Correspondence--Prince, Alice Shoreo 1946 (Box-folder 15:429)
    - Correspondence--Reid, Harry A. 1942-1944 (Box-folder 16:430)
    - Correspondence--Reid, J. Thomas 1949 (Box-folder 16:431)
    - Correspondence--Reynolds, T. H. 1949 (Box-folder 16:432)
    - Correspondence--Richardson, H. N. 1943 (Box-folder 16:433)
    - Correspondence--Richman, Luther A. 1943 (Box-folder 16:434)
    - Correspondence--Robinson, Grace 1950 (Box-folder 16:435)
    - Correspondence--Robinson, James H. n.d. (Box-folder 16:436)
    - Correspondence--Sampson, Rutherford B. 1949 (Box-folder 16:437)
    - Correspondence--Sandra 1949 (Box-folder 16:438)
    - Correspondence-- Savage, W. R. (Jr.); Suffolk Schools 1955 (Box-folder 16:439)
    - Correspondence--Sims, Pauline Jewett 1950 (Box-folder 16:440)
    - Correspondence--"Sis" 1948-1950 (Box-folder 16:441)
    - Correspondence-- (Box-folder 16:)
    - Correspondence--Slater, Annabel 1943 (Box-folder 16:442)
    - Correspondence--Smithey, David H.; Francis Wartman P. View 1941-1949 (Box-folder 16:443)
    - Correspondence--Smyler, Golda 1922 (Box-folder 16:444)
    - Correspondence--Spencer, James P. 1950-1952 (Box-folder 16:445)
    - Correspondence--Suezette 1946 (Box-folder 16:446)
    - Correspondence--Sylvia 1938 (Box-folder 16:447)
    - Correspondence-- (Box-folder 16:)
    - Correspondence--Taylor, N.D. 1943 (Box-folder 16:448)
    - Correspondence--Ted & Virginia 1948 (Box-folder 16:449)
    - Correspondence--Thompson, Corrine M. 1957 (Box-folder 16:450)
    - Correspondence--Thompson, Henrietta 1947-1948 (Box-folder 16:451)
    - Correspondence--Thompson, Marie E. 1926 (Box-folder 16:452)
    - Correspondence--Thronton, Jane 1920 (Box-folder 16:453)
    - Correspondence--Thursa 1929 (Box-folder 16:454)
    - Correspondence--Tinsley, J. M. (Dr.) 1950 (Box-folder 16:455)
    - Correspondence--Travis, Shirley 1952 (Box-folder 16:456)
    - Correspondence--Tucker, H.I. 1962 (Box-folder 16:457)
    - Correspondence--Turner, Lois M. n.d. (Box-folder 16:458)
    - Correspondence--"Unity" 1941-1952 (Box-folder 16:459)
    - Correspondence--Watkins, George W. 1962 (Box-folder 16:460)
    - Correspondence--Whielrds, B. Whillrds 1920 (Box-folder 16:461)
    - Correspondence--Williams, Camilla 1940-1950 (Box-folder 16:462)
    - Correspondence--Wilbur (99th) 1945 (Box-folder 16:463)
    - Correspondence--Wood, Alice 1955 (Box-folder 16:464)
    - Correspondence--Work, Agnes (Mrs.) 1923 (Box-folder 16:465)
    - Correspondence--Work, John 1943-1944 (Box-folder 16:466)
    - Correspondence--Worsham, Edmonia 1948 (Box-folder 16:467)
    - Correspondence--Wortman, Frances A. 1942 (Box-folder 16:468)
    - Correspondence--Wright, S.J. 1964 (Box-folder 16:469)
    - Correspondence-- (Box-folder 16:)
    - Correspondence--Wyatt, Ruth 1921 (Box-folder 16:470)
    - Correspondence--Wyllie, John Cook 1951 (Box-folder 16:471)
    - Correspondence--Young, H.C. 1951 (Box-folder 16:472)
    - Correspondence--Young, James 1942 (Box-folder 16:473)
    - Correspondence--Unreadable n.d. (Box-folder 16:474)
    - Correspondence--Fast, Howard 1946 (Box-folder 16:475)
    - Correspondence--Chesterfield Co. 1950 (Box-folder 16:476)
    - Correspondence--Forster, Jr. Louis 1944 (Box-folder 16:477)
    - Correspondence--Burghard, Cora 1948 (Box-folder 16:478)
    - Correspondence--Service, Russell 1954 (Box-folder 16:479)
    - Correspondence--Enrbar, Judson 1958 (Box-folder 16:480)
    - Correspondence--Smith, Harold F. 1941 (Box-folder 16:481)
    - Correspondence--Smith, James R. 1941-1944 (Box-folder 16:482)
    - Correspondence--Postcards 1931, 1940 (Box-folder 16:483)
    - Correspondence--Postcards 1943 (Box-folder 16:484)
    - Correspondence--Postcards 1945 (Box-folder 16:485)
    - Correspondence--Postcards 1946 (Box-folder 16:486)